

MALIK ABDUL AZIZ

085885099520 | malikaziz124@gmail.com

iln. kemang timur X, RT 008/RW003, bangka, mampang Prapatan, South Jakarta

I'am bachelor of computer science from Universitas Indraprasta PGRI Jakarta with GPA 3.26 have 5 years experience in food and beverage as crew part time. I like challenges, have a high curiosity and want to develop my skills especially in IT.

Work Experiences

PT wiryamanta sadina - Grha Intirub JI. Cililitan Besar No. 454 Jakarta 13650 Indonesia May 2018 - Aug 2023

Crew Part time

PT Wiryamanta Sadina (WS) was established in 2013 to operate the Wingstop franchise, the No. 1 chicken wings restaurant in the United States. Carrying the concept of fast casual dining served 'freshly made', food is made by order. Wingstop "The Flavor Experts" offers the best chicken delights and diverse taste experiences through 9 flavors of choice varian

- · run daily operational resturant
- · implement restaurant operational standard
- · manage products well in accordance with operational standards

PT Lotte Mart Shopping Indonesia - LOTTE Grosir Pasar Rebo Jalan Lingkar Luar Selatan Kav 6 Jakarta Timur - 13750

Mar 2016 - May 2016

apprenticeship

We enrich people's lives by providing superior products and services that our customers love and trust.

The Mission of LOTTE is to establish a foundation and baseline for our business activities. It plays a vital role in strengthening the pride and unity of our employees and motivating them to work for a united cause.

- · create price cards for each storefront
- · check the price of each item in the store to match the ongoing promo
- put up promo banners every time there is a new promo

Education Level

Universitas Indraprasta PGRI - Jl. Nangka Raya No.58 C, RT.5/RW.5, Tj. Bar., Kec.

Jagakarsa, Kota Jakarta Selatan, Daerah Khusus Ibukota Jakarta 12530

Bachelor Degree in computer science, 3.26/4.00

SMK Negeri 8 Jakarta - Komplek Depdikbud Jl. Raya Pejaten RT.06 RW.06, Kel. Jun 2015 - May 2018 Pejaten Barat, Kec.Pasar Minggu Jakarta Selatan 12510.

SMP Negeri 124 Jakarta - Jalan Duren Bangka No.23 Duren Tiga Pancoran, RT.6/

RW.4, Bangka, Kec. Pancoran, Kota Jakarta Selatan, Daerah Khusus Ibukota

Jakarta 12760

Jun 2012 - May 2015

Organisational Experience

Paskibra - Komplek Depdikbud Jl. Raya Pejaten RT.06 RW.06, Kel. Pejaten Barat, Kec.Pasar Minggu Jakarta Selatan 12510. Chairman

- manage the running of the organization
- · Create an event plan related to the organization

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- · Soft Skills: problem sloving, good communication, good leadership
- · Hobby: playing computer, listening to music, swimming